Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.20
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio, 1976-1993; XX.
  - Three Mile Island (TMI), 1979-1999; 5.
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference: Governor Thornburgh and President Carter Statements followed by Harold Denton (NRC) [online], April 1, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 369)
    - Three Mile Island Press (TMI) Conference (with Denton), April 2, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 370)
    - Three Mile Island Press (TMI) Conference (with Denton), April 3, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 371)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI)--Governor's Press Conference, April 3, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 372)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI)--Denton Press Briefing, April 4, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 373)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI)--Denton Press Briefing, April 5, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 374)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI)--Denton Press Briefing, 4 PM, April 6, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 375)
    - "A Report to the People on the Three Mile Island (TMI) Incident" [online], April 6, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 376)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI)--Governor's Press Conference, 3 PM, April 9, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 377)
    - Governor Thornburgh's Appearance before Senate Subcommittee regarding T Three Mile Island (TMI), April 23, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 378)
    - Thornburgh's Testimony regarding Three Mile Island (TMI), Washington, DC, August 21, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 379)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI): Did We Make It Worse Than It Was? 1979 RTNDA International Convention, Las Vegas, NV, September 6-8, 1979; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 380 381)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI): Six Months Later, AP Interview, September 19, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 382)
    - KYW TV Live Interview, Philadelphia; WIP Radio Interview, Philadelphia, September 25, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 383)
    - Governor Thornburgh's Meeting with the Three Mile Island (TMI) Alert Committee, October 22, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 384)
    - Energy and Three Mile Island (TMI) Ramifications: Governor Thornburgh's Speech to the National Association of Realtors, New Orleans Convention, November 9, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 385)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Speech at Republican National Governor's Conference with Questions and Answers, Austin, TX [online], November 18, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 386)
    - National Governors Association Trip to the Soviet Union: Press Conference regarding lessons of Three Mile Island (TMI), Harrisburg [online], December 4, 1979 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 387)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference, with DER, NRC, EPA, HEW, March 17, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 388)
    - Governor and Harold Denton's Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference, March 26, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 389)
    - Governor's Press Conference with the Union of Concerned Scientists regarding Three Mile Island (TMI) Clean-up, Harrisburg, March 29, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 390)
    - Governor's Meeting with Concerned Citizen's Group regarding Three Mile Island (TMI), April 8, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 391)
    - Governor's Press Conference with the Union of Concerned Scientists Report regarding Three Mile Island (TMI), May 14, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 392)
    - Governor's Press Conference regarding the Final Recommendation on Three Mile Island (TMI) Venting; Governor's Energy Council Press Briefing, May 16, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 393)
    - Governor's Press Conference regarding Three Mile Island (TMI) Venting, Harrisburg, June 26, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 394)
    - Governor's Press Conference following Three Mile Island (TMI) Venting Tour, June 30, 1980 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 395)
    - WGAL: Three Mile Island (TMI), March 18, 1981 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 396)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Conference: clean-up cost sharing plan, July 9, 1981 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 397)
    - Governor Thornburgh's Washington Press Interviews on Three Mile Island (TMI) Clean-Up, July 14, 1981 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 398)
    - Governor Thornburgh's Press Conference on Keystone State Games and Three Mile Island (TMI) Press Interview, March 30, 1982 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 399)
    - Governor Thornburgh's Three Mile Island (TMI) "Core Removal" Press Conference, April 7, 1982 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 400)
    - Panel Discussion of Three Mile Island (TMI) at the Kennedy School of Government; Boston, MA, March 23, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 401)
    - National Press Club Speech and Questions & Answers; Washington, DC [Three Mile Island (TMI)], March 28, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 402)
    - Three Mile Island (TMI): A Nuclear Accident Revisited; Panel Discussion, University of Pittsburgh, March 26, 1999; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 403 404)
  - Attorney General of the United States, 1988-1991; 6.
    - Keynote Address "Reinvigorating Government," Carnegie Mellon University (SUPA); Pittsburgh, PA, September 29, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 405)
    - U.S. Attorney's Conference Speech (Law Enforcement), Charleston, SC, October 8, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 406)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police Speech (Law Enforcement), Portland, OR, October 17, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 407)
    - Appeal of Conscience Speech (Drugs); NYC, October 18, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 408)
    - Franklin and Marshall College Dedication Ceremony, Lancaster, PA: Speech (Public Service) and Press Conference, October 20, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 409)
    - Organized Crime Drug Enforcement Task Force Speech (Drugs), San Diego, CA, October 25, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 410)
    - CBS: Streets Press Conference, October 27, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 411)
    - University of Florida Blue Key Banquet Speech (Drugs), Gainesville FL, October 28, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 412)
    - Oceans '88 Conference Speech (Environment), Baltimore, MD, October 31, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 413)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development Speech (Economy); Pittsburgh, PA, November 14, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 414)
    - New England Council Annual Dinner, Boston, MA, November 16, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 415)
    - U.S. Chamber of Commerce: Interview for Chamber's ESPN Business Report; Washington, DC, November 16, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 416)
    - Republican Governors Association Panel Discussion, November 21, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 417)
    - Federal Bar Council (medal awarded to AG); New York, NY, November 23, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 418)
    - Pennsylvania Manufacturer's Association Speech at the Pennsylvania Society (Awarded Gold Medal & Check for Rehabilitation Center of Pittsburgh), December 10, 1988 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 419)
    - Press Conference regarding Dropped Charges Against Lt. Col. North, January 5, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 420)
    - Business-Government Relations Council; Washington, DC, January 12, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 421)
    - Speech, 20th Annual Ecumenical Service, Martin Luther King Day; Ebenezer Baptist Church, Atlanta, GA, January 16, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 422)
    - Inauguration of Pennsylvania Attorney General Preate; The Forum, Harrisburg, PA, January 17, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 423)
    - NBC News "Meet the Press," Washington, DC, January 22, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 424)
    - Interview with Michael Wines of New York Times, April 18, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 425)
    - Questions and Answers at Breakfast with L.A. Times/Washington Bureau, February 15, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 426)
    - Council on Foreign Relations: Questions and Answers following Remarks, February 16, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 427)
    - Society of Four Arts Speech (drugs) and questions and Answers; Palm Beach, FL, February 21, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 428)
    - Economic Club of New York--Speech and Questions and Answers with Governor Kean; New York, NY, February 22, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 429)
    - National Governor's Association--Winter Meeting; Washington, DC, regarding funding to states for drugs and crime, February 27, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 430)
    - Association of American Publishers and American Booksellers--Questions and Answers following the Meeting, March 1, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 431)
    - West Virginia Bar Association: Speech and Questions and Answers; Charleston, WV, March 3, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 432)
    - Breakfast with Chicago Tribune/ Washington Bureau; Washington, DC, March 15, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 433)
    - Speech (drugs / morale) FBI and DEA Special Agents in Charge Conference; Phoenix, AZ, March 20, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 434)
    - National Law Enforcement Council; Washington, DC, March 21, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 435)
    - Press Availability from Kennedy School of Government, Boston, MA, March 23, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 436)
    - Questions and Answers at Breakfast; Washington, DC, March 30, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 437)
    - Closing Statements at the Italian-American Working Group at FBI Headquarters; Washington, DC, April 6, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 438)
    - Press Conference with Director Bennett regarding D.C. Drug Enforcement, April 10, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 439)
    - World Affairs Council of Pittsburgh: Speech (drugs) and Questions and Answers; Pittsburgh, PA, April 11, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 440)
    - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette Editorial Board, April 11, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 441)
    - Pittsburgh Press Editorial Board, April 11, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 442)
    - United Jewish Appeal Remarks and Questions and Answers, April 13, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 443)
    - Time Magazine Executive Press Conference Panel on Drug Policy; Washington, DC, April 17, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 444)
    - Breakfast with the Baltimore Sun, Washington Bureau; Washington, DC, April 19, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 445)
    - Speech at Foundation for Developmental Disabilities Dinner; San Diego, CA [online], April 20, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 446)
    - San Diego Union Editorial Board Meeting; San Diego, CA, April 21, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 447)
    - Speech (drugs) to Los Angeles World Affairs Council, Los Angeles, CA, April 24, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 448)
    - Los Angeles Street Gang Task Force at the DEA Offices; Los Angeles, CA, April 24, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 449)
    - Speech to International Drug Enforcement Conference (IDEC); Miami, FL, April 26, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 450)
    - International Drug Enforcement Conference (IDEC), Press Availability, Miami, FL, April 26, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 451)
    - Speech to Fifth and Eleventh Circuits Judicial Conferences; New Orleans, LA, May 8, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 452)
    - University of North Carolina (Chapel Hill) School of Law Commencement Address; Chapel Hill, NC, May 14, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 453)
    - George Washington University National Law Center Commencement Address; Washington, DC, May 21, 1989 (Box 1606, Cassette DTA 454)
    - Federal Judges Association; Washington, DC, May 23, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 455)
    - Police Executive Research Forum Remarks and Question and Answer; Rosalyn, VA, May 24, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 456)
    - DEA Memorial; Washington, DC, June 1, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 457)
    - Testimony before US Senate Committee on the Judiciary regarding role of American Bar Association (ABA) in judicial selection process, June 2, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 458)
    - DC Circuit Judicial Conference; Williamsburg, VA, June 6, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 459)
    - Delaware Bench and Bar Conference with Senator Joseph Biden and Attorney General Richard Thornburgh, June 7, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 460)
    - DEA Academy Graduation; Quantico, VA, June 9, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 461)
    - Houston Bank Fraud Conference; Houston, TX, June 13, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 462)
    - Speech (civil rights) to Houston Lawyers Association; Houston, TX, June 13, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 463)
    - Dallas Bank Fraud Conference; Dallas, TX and Speech (law enforcement) to Texas Police Association; Fort Worth, TX, June 13, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 464)
    - Galveston County Bar Association; Galveston, TX, June 13, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 465)
    - Speech (civil rights) to Operation Push Convention; Chicago, IL, June 27, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 466)
    - Ninth Circuit Judicial Conference; Thornburgh Keynote Speaker regarding "An Agenda for Justice," Laguna Nigel, CA [online], July 10, 1989; 2 audiocassettes. (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 467 468)
    - Attorney General's Working Group on Reducing Violence in America, July 12, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 469)
    - Speech (values) to American Legion; Pittsburgh, PA, July 12, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 470)
    - US Marshals Press Conference on Operation Stop (Street Terror Offender Program), July 17, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 471)
    - Speech (environment) to National District Attorneys Association Conferences; Portland, ME, July 19, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 472)
    - USA Today Editorial Board, July 24, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 473)
    - Speech (law enforcement) to American Bar Association (ABA) House of Delegates; Honolulu, HI, August 8, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 474)
    - Speech (law enforcement/prisons) to American Correctional Association; Baltimore, MD, August 14, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 475)
    - Milwaukee Journal and Sentinel Editorial Boards, August 17, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 476)
    - Colombians Most Wanted List Press Conference, August 22, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 477)
    - Federal Bar Association Tom Clark Award, Washington DC, August 25, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 478)
    - CBS News "Face the Nation", August 27, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 479)
    - Third Circuit Conference; Pittsburgh, PA, September 12, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 480)
    - Agudath Israel of America White House Briefing (with Mrs. Bush), September 14, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 481)
    - Coalitions for American Library Court, September 14, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 482)
    - Presidential Forum on Offenders with Mental Retardation, September 15, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 483)
    - Voice of America (VOA) Drug Conference, October 4, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 484)
    - Voice of America Drug Workshop: Dick Thornburgh Speaker regarding International Drug Trafficking (includes questions and answer session) [online], October 4, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 485)
    - Thornburgh's remarks regarding the historic first visit of the Attorney General of the United States to the Soviet Union, Moscow, Russia [online], October 14, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 486)
    - USSR Trip Discussing Rule of Law, October 19, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 487)
    - WGMS Radio "Capitol Commentary", October 23, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 488)
    - Senator John Heinz Meeting; Press Conference, October 24, 1989 and October 26, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 489)
    - Speech to Religious Alliance against Pornography, Omni-Shoreham; Washington, DC, October 26, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 490)
    - Speech to International Symposium on Money Laundering; Miami, FL, October 27, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 491)
    - Speech to Anti-Defamation League Civil Rights Committee; Philadelphia, PA, November 2, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 492)
    - NPR "All Things Considered" (with Nina Totenberg) regarding Special Prosecutor for HUD Secretary Pierce issue, November 2, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 493)
    - Speech "Rule of Law in USSR" to National Association of Women Judges, Washington, DC [online], November 10, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 494)
    - Organized Crime Drug Enforcement Task Force 1989 Conference, FL, November 14, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 495)
    - Speech (human rights, Soviet Jews) Council of Jewish Federations; Cincinnati, OH, November 18, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 496)
    - Announcement of Indictment of Marilyn Mill Harold, Closing Agent for HUD, November 21, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 497)
    - Trip to Luxembourg, December 13, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 498)
    - Rule of Law and Questions and Answers with the British/American Parliamentary Group, London, England, December 13, 1989 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 499)
    - Check Presentation towards Combat against Drug Traffic, January 7, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 500)
    - Speech (civil rights, ADA) to Office of Personnel Management Conference on Employing Persons with Disabilities; Bethesda, MD, January 10, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 501)
    - Speech (rule of law, separation of powers) to Federalist Society, Washington DC, January 19, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 502)
    - Speech to Society for the Reform of Criminal Law, Washington DC, January 22, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 503)
    - Testimony before Federal Courts Study Committee, January 31, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 504)
    - Time Magazine, Washington Bureau, February 1, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 505)
    - Speech to Governor's Alcohol and Other Drugs Conference; Des Moines, IA, February 8, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 506)
    - Linn County Bar Association; Cedar Rapids, IA and Washington Times Editorial Board, February 8, 1990 and February 14, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 507)
    - Economic Crime Council Meeting; Washington, DC, February 22, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 508)
    - Speech (racial issues, civil rights) to Wiesenthal Center's National Leadership Conference, March 6, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 509)
    - Godfrey Sperling Breakfast, Washington DC, March 7, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 510)
    - United States Attorneys visits, Nashville and Memphis, TN, March 9, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 511)
    - Speech (public service) to University of Tennessee Law Review Banquet; Knoxville, TN, March 10, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 512)
    - Freedom of Information Act, March 16, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 513)
    - Bush Administration and Press, March 16, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 514)
    - VOA Drug Conference, March 19, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 515)
    - Speech (drugs) Greater Spokane Substance Abuse Council Luncheon; Spokane, WA, March 22, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 516)
    - Speeches Stanford Law Review and Palo Alto Jaycees (drugs, public service), March 22, 1990 and March 23, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 517)
    - Boston and Prince George County, MD (asset forfeiture), March 26, 1990 and March 29, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 518)
    - University of Pittsburgh Law School Speech (Rule of Law in Soviet Union), April 3, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 519)
    - Virginia Drug Summit Speech (war on drugs, valor); Richmond, VA, April 16, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 520)
    - Ixtapa Press Conference, Ixtapa, Mexico, April 17, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 521)
    - Speech (white collar crime) to Texas Bar Association; DEA/FBI SAC Conference; San Antonio, TX, April 21, 1990 and April 23, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 522)
    - Dallas: multiple events, April 23, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 523)
    - American Black Forum and American Legislative Exchange Council, April 25, 1990 and April 27, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 524)
    - Albuquerque, and Santa Fe, New Mexico speeches, May 2, 1990 and May 3, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 525)
    - Speeches: Ohio State Law School Graduation and the 60th Anniversary of the Federal Bureau of Prisons, Washington, DC, May 12, 1990 and May 14, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 526)
    - Speech (alternatives to incarceration) to National Conference on State and Local Drug Policy (ONDCP), May 15, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 527)
    - Washington Post editorial board, May 17, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 528)
    - Delaware Governors Club, White House Briefing, May 21, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 529)
    - Procurement Fraud Conference (DOJ) and President's Drug Advisory Council Dinner, May 21, 1990 and May 22, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 530)
    - National Center for the Public Interest "Day With Justice"; Washington, DC, May 29, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 531)
    - Salt Lake City and the University of Pittsburgh, multiple events, May 31,1990 and June 21, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 532)
    - Speech (values) to National Sheriffs' Association; Denver, CO, June 26, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 533)
    - Los Angeles and Orange County multiple events, June 27, 1990 and June 28, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 534)
    - USA Today Interview and Speech (Reach of the Law) to Lincoln Club of Orange County, June 28, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 535)
    - Law Enforcement Meeting, June 28, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 536)
    - San Diego World Affairs Council, June 28, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 537)
    - "Off the Record Club" Luncheon, Washington DC, July 11, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 538)
    - Speech (judicial improvement) to Eighth Circuit Judicial Conference; Kansas City, KS, July 20, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 539)
    - American Legislative Exchange Council Annual Meeting; Boston MA, July 27, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 540)
    - Chicago Sun Times Editorial Board, August 6, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 541)
    - Questions and Answers following speech to ABA Annual Meeting regarding Judicial Appointments and ABA Participation; Chicago, IL [online], August 6, 1990 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 542)
  - Campaign for U.S. Senate, 1991; 7.
    - Thornburgh for Senate Ads: Western Pennsylvania [online], Fall, 1991 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 543)
    - Dick Thornburgh for Senate Ads: "Damage", Fall, 1991 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 544)
    - Debate #1: Wofford and Thornburgh, September 6, 1991 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 545)
    - Debate #2: Wofford and Thornburgh, October 18, 1991 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 546)
  - Under-Secretary-General United Nations, 1993; 8.
    - BBC Interview regarding Thornburgh's experience at the United Nations [online], August, 1993 (Box 1607, Cassette DTA 547)